welcome to the dyar comedy podcast the
only podcast where you can hang out with
your favorite dry bar comedians hey that
sounds pretty good hey Jordan that
sounds nice man sounds nice
partner partners in crime even and host
uh I'm Taylor neelon I'm Jordan Megan
happy to be here me too thanks for
having me yet again me too we had dinner
at your house last night you did it was
nice for you to come over you didn't
know about that right yeah it was very
nice of you it nice to get to know you
personally not just in this professional
setting people been commenting that our
dynamic's offputting so we needed we
were trying to overcome that
actually but we got such an interesting
guess we should just jump to the clip
right I think let's go to the clip man
it is true it is true I'm a recovering
addict man people are thrown when they
hear it uh which is understandable I
don't really look the part this whole
thing ain't really
screaming heroin addict I look more like
Woody harelson with a thyroid problem
or a middle-aged Cabbage Patch but uh
it's true I got 12 years clean now man
and uh
yeah thank
you I just I just throw that in there
when I want an Applause
break it's true though man and I'm clean
and sober now and people think that I
don't use drugs that I'm like against
drugs which isn't true you know I think
every drug has a practical use like
alcohol is a great disinfectant heroin
is an amazing painkiller
meth is perfect for when you need to
disassemble the lawn mower and use use
its blades to kill the Goblins that live
in the
[Laughter]
wall well you know him you love him from
his specials dream catcher and what you
just saw from addicted to Comedy welcome
to the podcast Andy gold I'm glad that
clip wasn't any longer you're you're
killing In that clip I love it when it
jump cut to the audience in the whole
front row it looked like they cast a
cocoon can't we put the old people in
the
back that's so funny we were talking
about how audience shots at dry bar very
specific do everything we can to let
them like dry bar this is who the 80
year people who
are Korean War
veterans that's nice you give the
veterans a spot at the front of your
shows and were good but it's like
talking to these people about like
heroin they were into it yeah yeah they
they were great the dreyar Crowds
Are unbelievably nice they're a
difficult bunch to to bomb in front of
Taylor was saying that 35% of our
podcast listeners are 65 and
older yeah I think uh 30% yeah 30% or 65
and old we're introducing them to they
probably know what podcasts were until
just
now and now they now they have you
coming in real hot at the beginning of
the
episode so I was uh doing a little bit
of research for this podcast okay just
to see what it's all about thank you for
coming prepared yeah and I
uh this is the first comment I read can
I read it to you guys
please sadly I don't like The Two
Hosts I love dry bar videos but this
podcast is difficult to endure dot dot
dot because of The Two
Hosts whoa yeah can I say I don't agree
thank you also why do you think it's
difficult to endure it's not these
people Nothing in life should make you
sad enough to make that kind of comment
I see stuff online that I dislike a lot
I just scroll and move my life but some
people like well I need to let this be
known that this is I don't I don't like
this and they get on and type it and
walk away proud of themselves
like and yeah none of the comedians are
going to read that and be like dang I
guess I'm going to stop hosting the
podcast yeah I would never think that
also I think you two guys are lovely
thank you I don't agree just to
illuminate the uh that's so funny I will
say we we try not to shine too bright so
that our our guests can shine that's
right we bu down our personalties like
we could we could shine harder I guess
my favorite part is how she
reemphasized I don't like The Two Hosts
I normally like dry bar videos but I
don't like this dot dot dot
because of the twoos yeah it was like a
Biblical kmus almost of the repeating on
the ends well on my first special I
think I must have read I read the
comments everybody says not yes I do and
I engage and there were so many people
just straight up saying this is the
worst comedian I've ever seen in my life
and then people would go defend me and
then what I would do is I would take the
side of the people who hated me against
the people who defended me they like no
I think he's great great like no I agree
with Martha this was a really bad
special you have bad taste and would
they engage with you after that I think
they were really befuddled by it right
yeah I found if few engage with haters I
usually don't comment back cuz I will do
that too and I'll usually be like kind
of sarcastically nice or overly nice
it's my tactic usually which make me
makes me look pathetic but that's kind
of my idea yeah I I I should uh say I
used to engage a lot more I've stopped
now like my second dry bar special I
didn't do it nearly as much but on my
first I don't know if you remember I
made a video of all of their profile
pictures uh and made a music video to
the Hulk Hogan theme song just showing
all of the profile pictures of all of my
meanest comments wow so you don't get
away scotch free on scotch free I
believe it's I believe it's scotf free
isn't it like Scotch like the like the
tape brand yeah it's also a a kind of
whiskey I'm pretty sure it's Scot free
yeah but the saying is not about Scotch
tape Scot free but that doesn't make it
make any more sense no it's about tape
well you know people always give out
tape for free in your mind you're
getting away easily because you're not
taped to something you're getting away
scotch free where if you tap to the
wall how does SC how does scotf Frey
make any more sense I I don't know think
it's
let's do it right now yeah can we look I
think it's maybe in reference to Scott
Scotsman Scots people oh yeah it
probably
has you thought Scotts aren't that's not
a racist well I'm just saying it's
probably going to have some derogatory
mean SC origin I think it's okay to make
fun okay the expression scottf free with
one t originates from the Scandinavian
word scat which means tax or payment ah
so Scott which means you're getting away
free of tax what does scotch free mean
though there is no scotch free so you
thought it was scotch free because
people give away
tape I that was me double ding down when
I I didn't want to be wrong did you say
double ding down double ding down it's
double ding
down you've never heard double ding down
you're not getting away scotch free on
this one I'm double ding down on this
one I think people occasionally give you
a piece of tape when you need it but I
don't think tape necessarily has a rep
utation for being a thing that people
are just giving away for free like water
or
something
wow scotch free it's a regional dialect
thing I think
a where you from again you're just a 26y
old kid man I'm Scotland yeah I thought
the word uh naked was naked with an M
until I was like 17 you thought it naked
was as an amaz and monkey like I don't
want I hate Jim you got to shower and
get
naked nobody corrected you huh not until
like high school were you raised in like
a kind of more oral
tradition rather than seeing words
written down how did you not never see
the word naked written by the AG that's
a good question um that's a really good
question my mom was a big-time reader my
dad was not uh I read a fair amount but
yeah make it I would say
I don't want to go in there and be
naked well what was the I probably just
like when I was reading Hatchet or
whatever as a kid and they said naked I
was like oh that's a word I don't
know I just had no deductive reasoning
didn't connect I would swim naked in the
lake I like what does it mean to one
naked you know what naked
means what was that what was the one
thing that your your family did with the
shotgun that was not like you calling
shotgun for car that Wonder this thing
outside we bring this up in every
episode and uh my family when we were
calling for shotgun the front seat in
the car we would say no spits no rocks
you ever do this have you heard of this
um my thing was no battle but I just
never got shotgun I was the youngest oh
okay yeah and even now as adults my
brothers are all 6'3 and 6'4 and I'm
5'10 5'11 in shoes so I still I'm the
permanent backseat guy okay it's a shame
you could have called for a battle see I
think the no spits no rocks is just a
more specific we're saying what the
battles are what is spits I think it's
who can spit the furthest oh or farthest
but you also said it never came down to
actually spit no you just you just
because you always said you would say no
spits no rocks and therefore you cannot
that leaves it open to other battle
challenges though no battles is kind of
no battles a lot more my family was not
very creative when it came to battles so
we we had two battles that were
longstanding traditions and how many
siblings did you have I'm the fourth of
five you're the fourth of five so not
quite the youngest all brothers or
sisters my oldest is my sister and then
I have four brothers but we're a weird
family where I mean I don't if it's
weird my the oldest three were all born
like a year apart then it was seven
years and I was born oh wow and then
four years my little brother was born so
there's a big gap there but so you're
kind of uh only child Vibes a little bit
when your brothers and sisters went off
to college were you ever kind of by
yourself I mean I always had my little
brother there so now but yeah there was
a while we at home it was just me and my
little brother were you nice to him yeah
we get along actually closest thing I
had to a little brother was my cousin
Levi who was a bed weaer and when he
when he came to visit I would make him
sleep in the tub my mom got soad I can't
believe you're making Levi sleep in of
the bed wedding yeah I shouldn't say his
name everybody's got a cousin Levi you
know he's the kind of kid who would
listen to a dry bar comedy
too we can he he older than 65 what was
that is he older than 65 no he's uh my
age okay oh I get this was a reference
yeah that's a call back um I don't care
you can leave it in shouts out cousin
you're not wet in the bed anymore you're
doing good uh you got a nice wife and
family and everything so you know he
came out he came out all right he's not
out there killing hitchhikers like the
other bed wers that's bed wers get a bad
rap and it's like besides even the bed
wedding it goes beyond well
do people know what we're talking about
I take on a a guilty until proven
innocent attitude with bed wers I don't
I if I know that about you I'm going to
I'm going to assume that you're probably
a little Disturbed and you got an uphill
battle against me and I encourage other
people to also look at you with a
suspicious eye right I'm going to reveal
I was I was go to bad weather till too
late in life until How old uh I don't
know on air it it was it was 65 or older
but to me what I think it was is as a
child 65y old they go full
circle as a child I just slept so
peacefully yeah and start when I started
learning about the anxieties of life
that's when my body would actually wake
up but when I had no cares as a child I
would just sleep through everything
would just release yeah just so I think
it was more I think if you're bed weding
you're just so peaceful at with the
world that I think that that was your
story right the thing we're talking
about is there's like serial killer
profiles show that that people who the
bed growing up be are like because
conversations like these are happening
everywhere and what else are they
supposed to do this and fire starters so
I was a fire starter I I wish too when I
was a kid yeah Fire's cool yeah it's
alluring yeah and it's uh it scares me
well man you want to come over and start
a fire with me sometime I don't really
actually yeah but if you think about it
if there's one person who's safe
starting a fire it's someone who also
wets a bed CU you can then put the fire
out
Taylor what I mean I'm making
connections I hate to Stomp all over
your lodic this podcast but if you wet
the bed you're out of fluid brother oh
that's true you got to retain that in
the night so you can pee on the fire
your cousin did you give him blankets in
the bathtub a garbage sack put a garbage
sack on the bathro which was doubly
insulting that'll turn him into a serial
killer want P to get on the on the
tub I mean there's also a thing with
seial killers and bathtubs too is there
well yeah the I don't know how detailed
we want to be like if you want need to
dispose of a body then you probably want
to go to the bathtub and if you want to
talk about this stuff you probably don't
want to do it on the 65 or older dyar
comedy podcast too but anyway I think
there's a g g G-rated way to do it talk
about disposing of a body did I do it
yeah okay and I'm can I continue cuz I
thought about this yeah please do okay
so I would take it up in the mountains
and bury the body about 10 ft deep
extremely deep okay and then at the
bottom of the hole I would have all
kinds of kindling and Tinder you know
very Tinder Tinder very flammable Uh
Wood and this would be at night then I
would light it and let it burn and sort
of cremate the body and the Holes Dig
enough deep enough so people couldn't
see the flames and it's at night time so
people couldn't see the smoke then after
it burns for a few hours I would just
put a bunch of top soil and dirt on it
and plant a quaking gaspen tree which
are indigenous here to Utah they can
grow up in the mountains without much
care they're going to BL right in with
all the Aspen Groves and they're going
to send off Runners and everything like
that and then they grow about 6 feet a
year I worked at a garden center for
River I know a lot about trees and in a
few years time not even a few years time
that corpse is just going to be lost in
a whole root system of quakies they'll
never find them it's kind of like a a
cage like over the the body right like
the roots would come out and like make
it hard to dig through and just to make
it dry bar appropriate I would only do
this to an R-rated stand-up
ched I wouldn't do this to a good
guy thank you for that caveat makes me
feel better about this episode how do
you think it's going so far I think it's
going good I I'm really enjoying it yeah
I'm having a good time do you think that
going back to comments mean comments one
thing I've noticed with the with dry bar
commenters is there's a variety of mean
comments that are nice mean where it's
they're it's very respectful but they're
letting you know I think one that we saw
was like don't really care for this
format and then they put a flower emoji
at the end
yes can't be mad at that it's so bizarre
to me one comment I got was somebody was
telling me to be more of a
Storyteller rather and I was like
well you prefer storytelling that's fine
but that's my style is kind of jokey
yeah and I'm like I I don't think they
really understand it's sort of the
equivalent of asking
like somebody who sings rock and roll to
sing hip-hop you know you're you're
saying do this other style that I like
telling Steph Curry he should dunk more
yeah telling Steph Curry he should dunk
more Andy if you could equate yourself
in your comedy to an NBA player who
would you equate it
to I don't know ooster
tag why my oer tag good enough to be a
starter but no nobody I don't know who
that is yeah maybe I'll end up on a
billboard for donating a kidney to a
sister or
something you know he was on the Utah
Jazz finals run teams back in the 90s he
was our Center OH interesting he just
like kind of a big country boy Shaquille
oil would look at Greg ooster tag and
salivate I don't think I ever saw Shaq
scored less than
40 against Oster tag Jerry SLO had to
put Carl Malone on Shaq Carl Malone
gives up four inches to Shaq but Oster
tag was just pitiful get demolish yeah
my dad called him ooster
Pig and when we went to live jazz games
people would boo oer Tech okay serious
answer I don't know um maybe Rodman cuz
I feel like I'm really good at getting
into people's heads you're a lot
antagonistic I like I love that about
watching you perform is that you have
this weird dynamic with the audience
where I don't I don't know how to
totally explain it there's a little bit
of inks there but there's kind of like
this over the top niess sometimes too
and a little there's this tension that
you build with the audience that I
really enjoy oh thank you does that ring
true to you or am I talking I I I see
what you're saying um yeah I can be kind
of confrontational with the audience
yeah but I'm like cheerful yeah yeah it
makes me laugh was that something you
learned to do like no it's totally
hopefully now that I'm mindful of it it
doesn't become something I try to do and
become contrived cuz it just sort of
happened naturally and I think Jordan is
right but I never even didn't even
really occur to me until just now don't
let it get in your head and ruin your a
exactly no I'm serious cuz uh when you
try to do stuff it always becomes
contrived I think whenever you
like try to do stuff that the audience
likes like when you're writing a
joke for the purpose of I hope people
like this it's always G to feel like
contrived and needy and pandering a
little pandering and you're selling it
and throwing the salesmanship at the
audience and I just think you don't
really know what going to work so just
do what you think is funny and what you
believe
in
and and use the audience feedback to
adjust that appropriately but don't be
like only thinking about how this person
will like a joke or not yeah beforehand
then you'll be joking about like
somebody said to me hey uh I thought I
have an idea for your roast videos I'm
like oh great he goes you should roast
uh The Bachelor
contestants I don't watch The Bachelor
he's like yeah but it's really popular
and PE people would like it like that's
never how I want to do comedy right like
the internet even more so you don't know
what's going to work just do what you
think is funny and if it hits great and
if it doesn't let keep doing what you
think is funny but you can tell when
comedians are doing like oh I hope this
becomes big and to me it's always
embarrassing yeah yeah especially if it
flops yeah sometimes it does work and
but we as comedians can kind of be like
I don't want to do it but even when it
works and it it works a lot sometimes
cuz you're saying especially if uh you
have a lot of energy and Charisma and
you're saying things that people like to
hear and agree with and they'll clap and
and like I I'll just be in the back of
the room just like oh well that's just
hack yeah BS uh whatever material right
you know so how did we get going on that
I don't know but you mentioned your
roast videos which we do want to talk
about a little bit Yeah cuz you've
gotten a big following I I was with you
as you the followers were coming in by
the thousands we were hanging out in a
green room where you post pictures of uh
children and you roast them yeah and
it's really funny yeah um that's yeah
and then after a while people started
submitting photos which is nice because
I don't have to go find them but to me
like the it the funniest element of the
rast is now gone which was like yo who's
this like 40-year-old making fun of
little
kids now that the kids are in on the
joke that element is gone yeah but
you're still doing it right yeah and I'm
still having fun doing it um people
email me photos I get tons every day
most of them I I don't
use the most important thing is the
photo just has to look good yeah like
even if you were a really funny looking
kid people will take a picture of like a
Polaroid with their phone holding it at
an angle with like a glare on it yeah
and then those are always the people who
keep responding hey just want to make
sure you didn't forget it and I'd be
like your picture is bad let's get you a
scanner digitize these yeah I can't I
can't use it that's what do you
I mean you like you said you don't want
to analyze it too much what you're doing
but what do you like about roasting kid
photos
um I like that it's mean and it's
punching down and that kids are
defenseless shamelessly yeah like I just
think there's something really funny
about a grown-up making fun of kids yeah
I've always made fun of kids when I was
at the Angels game with remember
Christian yeah there was these like
Junior High kids sitting in front of us
who were all excited about the baseball
game and I was just making fun of them
all game and I like who's this guy being
mean to
us they're not used to like a grownup
making fun of you've been preparing
yourself for a long time for these
videos to well well I it's fun people
that get offended at the videos because
you have had some people that are like
oh yeah but these are also old photos
that it's not like you're it's different
than the Angels game CU you're not
actually talking to these children that
you're making fun of 100% like I'm not
totally heartless I don't want some like
seven-year-old to be scrolling on his
phone and to see a video with like
500,000 views and 200 comments of him
getting made fun of like I don't want
that so I make sure they're all
grown-ups now yeah and I also like if
you're a grownup and you can't laugh at
photos of yourself when you were a kid
right like
yikes because one gal actually emailed
me and I posted that photo it was a good
one then she emailed back I guess it was
her cousin and her cousin was Furious
saying hey can you take it down my
cousin thought I was
joking and I didn't take it
down cuz I feel like first of all the
video was doing
well but I also I I really don't feel
bad for her just cuz you're like all
butt hurt and sad doesn't actually mean
you have a point like this will be good
for
you so you're not
heartless she's an adult she's a grownup
I think I just think she's wrong yeah I
mean talk about an innocuous thing to
get offended
about like making fun of an old
childhood photo like you take yourself
that seriously yeah so it actually made
me resent her as a person and kind of
they brought up a oh sorry I should have
interrupted you but no no that's okay I
I think I remember some of the jokes I
said she looks like a some of I I use a
lot of obscure references I think she
looked like a uh a replicant from uh
Blade Runner
yeah and WWF IC Champion Mr Perfect some
the other it's kind of an older one I
guess none of them are really old I've
only been doing it for like three
months yeah I'm putting myself in the
shoes if it you were doing current kids
and I was like a second grader and I got
on the internet and just saw pictures of
myself being roasted and that would just
I don't know I don't I wouldn't be able
to process it as a tri no that's why I
make sure they're all old and also I do
use Almost 100% photos that are
submitted to me now just to escape some
of the heat like why are you bullying
these kids right you know but it hasn't
really worked I still get plenty of com
comments like coming at me yeah and
people like why don't you roast your own
photos I'm like I did just keep
scrolling was that the was that the
first ones you did or did would that
come I did that after like a month or
two when like lots of people commented
I'd like to see you when you you were a
kid and I was a funny looking kid every
nobody looks that's what well in times
change I was 90s so '90s I had the bull
cut sometimes all the way around beetles
style and then sometimes parted down the
middle like 7th Heaven and I had that
one I had steps too you steps I had the
steps dud yes one of my brother my
brother was another redhead with
steps yeah really see I'm a I'm a
kind of a redhe head light the beard is
redder than the head hair yeah you have
Aesthetics of a redheaded person but
then you have very blond hair yeah so I
feel your pain a little bit I I get some
of the ginger
comments um and I get old women who are
excited about it oh yeah we were talking
about so much old you had a joke about
this and the same thing happened to you
this old woman showed me a picture of
her redheaded grandchild like I'm like
whoa what a cool redheaded kid another
one yeah does anybody else have any
redheaded kids I can look at I just go
through life hoping oh man I hope
somebody shows me a photo of their
redheaded kid today I feel so valued in
scene right now CU I have red hair
that's they like touching red hair too
old people really yeah you never had
that no your isn't read enough they're
so fascinated by it I don't I don't
understand it assuming it feels
different too than regular hair of a
different color you're the kind of guy
who would like him touch your hair you
let the you let the old women at your
hair is that why you grew it out in the
back so there was some easily accessible
hair just they don't to reach Jordan is
so nice that he'll let them
sure I'm a people pleaser in the end and
what do you say when they compliment it
softness or you're like oh thanks yeah
it's nice to hear that your hair's soft
I don't know I just it's never like may
I touch it it's just I it's not as much
as I've been an adult but definitely as
a kid like like oh look at this red hair
and just the hands already going
through I had a red-headed grandchild
once my my brother who was a super
redhead like you uh he's not as good of
a sport about it but I think it's
because he was incessantly bullied um
moved into this new neighborhood and you
know how bullying when you're a kid is
just random they'll just like pick a kid
to bully yeah and they bullied my
brother like crazy and I think what
really made it worse was my brother was
a great athlete he went on to play
college baseball and he was drafted by
the Cubs actually oh cool yeah um
phenomenal
pitcher and he was always striking out
his bullies like dominating them and I
think that really made them hate him
even more for sure cuz like wait a
minute this kid's supposed to be the
nerd and he was better at basketball
them too um baseball was really his game
uh but imagine uh the kid that you're
bullying just strikes you out for years
like for years this went all through
elementary junior high and high school
like easily and I think that
really like set the rage into high gear
yeah
so like he's normal and he has a happy
life and everything but he still gets a
little triggered by the word ginger he's
like I hate that
word yeah that's funny yeah I do jokes
about I was never really
bullied about my red hair but it is a
weird thing that people have picked on
and South Park made huge about the
gingers don't have souls thing it's just
then it became so hack yeah right that
that's the part that bothers me is
people will say you're to
Ginger with this self assured
smirk like they just said something so
ingenious y like that's been so played
for 15 years now yep okay what NBA
player would you say you are me yes oh
compared to Comedy uh uh I I think I'm
like a Boris Dia
okay why because he never seem that in
shape and he just kind of was there to
facilitate and throw the ball it was
just kind of a nice guy to be around who
did he play for uh he was on the Jazz
for a minute but Spurs he was on Spurs
what I don't remember where he was
actually was he on the Bobcats when back
on the Bobcat days this is deep cut NBA
stuff but yeah I think he was a bit of a
journeyman yeah yeah I just know that he
when he moved
to Utah it was in his contract they had
to pay for all he had a giant wine
seller wherever he was before and it was
specific they had a certain amount of
money allocated to move his wine seller
to Utah wow how how French of
him
truly we got a we've got a visual aid
too yeah we're killing with the visual
aid really listening that's him when he
was with San Antonio yeah he got he got
a little chubbier yeah later like he's
pointing at you too JM he does any other
players that uh are more notable that
the people might might know for my for
me I mean I just I I barely relate to
him because I'm just not athletic at all
but I love basketball yeah yeah I don't
know
yeah let me think who would I I think
you would have be a better assessment
outside looking in at my com who would I
say Jordan Mak is in the
NBA um
um let's see I'm thinking I'm trying to
think of somebody crafty gets the job
done maybe a little bit too
nice
um give me a minute here you guys we got
all the time in the world we got time
they can edit this out if I I take too
long to think here I'm trying to think
of somebody good because you're a good
comedian thank you
um not Luke Walton he's too much of a
weirdo we're going to make you Dennis
Johnson point guard for the Boston
Celtics in the 1980s I like that you
went with somebody more well-known and
very you know like very solid like was
kind of uh the glue that held that
Celtics team together yeah uh
competent um but
forgettable I knew there was a punch
com I was feeling good for a minute how
would you what what NBA player are you
for improv comedians Taylor
um
um Shaq he's so
funny like me Shaq he he used to be
funny he is really settled into being a
bitter old contous man yeah I don't
really like listen to be honest he is
like you
actually the bitterness checks out yeah
always says words wrong they close
enough know what he's talking about yeah
and kind of a deeper voice kind of
mumbling through things that's yeah
that's what I do you do have a sh voice
you got a good deep voice what about you
guys who actually know the NBA what
would you say I am I'm not that familiar
with your improv Taylor dog on it yeah
but I saw your standup so I would
compare you to uh darl Dawkins he was
very imaginative and
Whimsical that's Taylor yes and didn't
really
seem like uh he was Guided by
reality yeah how does one whimsically
play basketball just just like a um
naming his dunks he was just out there
trying to express himself oh yeah and
would often deliberately break
backboards just cuz you thought yeah
it's almost like he was playing
basketball
ironically yeah yeah that checks out the
cake maker the baby maker the wh bams
thank you man yes I am jam slam were all
were all of his dunks yeah he's the
first player to wear gold chains in a
game yeah then that might be Jordan
right are we can we pop him out are you
yeah do you know this is the new Part of
Me Andy are you sporting gold now I I
have a have a little chain now let's hit
pull it let it let it just know I won't
I wouldn't normally wear it out I like
having I like having a little peak of
chain and people go whoa what's he
hiding I like it though out I I think in
is The Right Move yeah um it works well
with the black sweater a lot I think
yeah I used to ro I feel I feel really
self-conscious with that I'm going to
put it back dude when I was a kid in my
early 20s and late teens this is like
when 50 Cent In gunit was big uhh I
sported ridiculous chains love and
armbands and puffy vests and Echo yeah I
fantastic was a very much a hip-hop kid
but chains kind of seem like chains like
that they're making a bit of a comeback
yeah I don't know if I love being
associated with the people that I see
also wearing chains but it's it's always
called to me yeah and the Adrian my wife
gave this to me as my Christmas present
I think you kind of no BS I think you
kind of pull it off thank you do do you
put it on every day or do you sleep in
it or how does that work um it's I I
technically could shower with it on but
that's the only time I take it off but
it's supposed to be tarnish
free the brand is called uh King ice oh
jeez that's perfect that's your
nickname and I like the long hair too
thanks are you going to keep keep
growing it what happens with my hair is
that I get to a point where I'm annoyed
take I I I hate getting haircuts just
cuz I don't really like the
experience and but then it's how
annoying is it to get my hair in order
cuz when I wake up in the morning my
hair is very thick and it's just out
here I look insane so it takes a lot of
work to get it down it's got a nice I
might cut I might uh I think I might
like I like the length I might trim it a
little bit the viewers ever the viewers
ever even seen the back of your head
maybe that could be something you could
show is that a patreon thing maybe Pat
okay I don't need the comments by the
back of my head patreon for the back of
Jordan but I do think we need to have
you uh if you're willing to roast some
younger pictures of us I'll try my roast
videos are not Improv like Chuck D said
he goes I don't freestyle much but I
write it like
such so we'll try see let's see we'll
see let get Taylor's up there where
where's it at T yeah yeah that's just
2008 emo Fallout Boy Justin
Bieber you look like every other
kid like one of Drake and Josh's friends
or something from the Disney
ch you kind of look like a tad pull a
little
bit what are you doing right there um
I'm pretty sure this is the last day of
seventh grade or something last day of
seventh grade yeah yeah you're just kind
of a basic 2007 gray cray kid with that
haircut everybody else had that haircut
the haircut all the kids have now is
like this Jane Fonda thing my nephew has
it where it's really fluffy in the front
and the top yeah I like that and that
was the
haircut yeah it's the total Justin
Bieber it was yeah Bieber inspired yeah
so that's that's the kind of picture
that if somebody submitted to me I
probably wouldn't end up
using that's the
ultimate too boring Taylor yeah you got
some Goods I see the follow it looks
like a kid who would like oh I'm going
to do improv at
BYU but then didn't make it into BYU oh
you day no no I didn't really what I
almost went to BYU I almost transferred
what school did you go to UVU UVU Utah
Valley Unity Valley University yeah
they're D1 aren't they yeah know they
are yeah so Utah has a lot of D1 schools
yeah it's kind of wild Utah State Weber
the U the Y Utah Tech is too also Utah
Tech is D1 as far as basketball goes
because they're the they're the same
conference as UVU wow all right we'll
get Jordan
this local College talk here we go think
you would have chosen this one this is
one I could write some stuff the thing
is the reason I like to sit down and and
write jokes about it is I don't like to
say like the obvious thing I would try
to avoid kind of the red hair but yeah
you look sort of like
a like a b like a ball boy at the North
Pole I look very gingery in that picture
I don't think I look as gingery
right now as I do in that picture yeah
you uh I would definitely say something
about the lack of
eyebrows you got hazed they your
teammates waxed off your eyebrows at
basketball
camp I think he's trying to give me a
hint to go after the
teeth yeah there my diastema was uh
quite intense what's diasa that's a the
Gap in the middle if you have a gap in
the middle of your two teeth it's called
a Dias di there multiple problems not
just the
Gap they're going in different
directions for sure did you ever get
braces I did and then I I stopped
wearing my retainer I so I still have a
little bit of a diasta it's not as bad
me too me too man thing about the uh the
heavy duty gingers is they actually have
eyebrows they're just invisible
translucent yeah my arm hair like my AR
you can't really see it I do have arm
hair but it's
very yeah see I'm not great uh riffing
off the top of my head people say stand
up is harder than improv but I've always
felt like improv is
harder do you want to do other picture
sure let's see the other picture why
not okay yeah it's uh this is closer to
my picture a little was this Trek it
might have been T it was definitely some
sort of scout or wouldn't you be in
Pioneer Garb if that was Trek though the
Pioneers don't have Puka shell
necklaces um so now you're wearing the
gold chain and before you were in the
puka showell yeah that's it's how old
were you right there uh it's hard to I
don't totally know I I look like a
teenager I would say and you're sporting
the braces right there too braces yeah
it's got kind of a Dutch angle on this
picture I don't
know yeah what's going on what's that
what's to do with that what is the do
with that call Taylor if you're vers in
film Theory you know these Dutch angles
often unsettled viewer show but I think
your picture's doing that
enough did you take film Theory at see I
really I'm sorry to disappoint I I
really take 10 minutes when I get the
pictures and sit down and write the
jokes oh you I think you did
great um uh yeah I I got I have a minor
in Humanities which I got it just so I
could tell my friends my film opinions
were more legitimate than theirs I like
talking about movies yeah we talk you
you're very well read Andy gold and I
remember driving to Rock Springs Wyoming
with you
and I was uh it was more important to me
when I was younger that people thought I
was
smart I've gotten a little bit more
comfortable in my own skin as I've
gotten older and I don't need to tell
people about all the books I've read
well I didn't feel like you're flexing
this what we were talking about you're
talking about cormic McCarthy novels and
that's still true I'm still an absolute
freak for cormi McCarthy do you know
cormi McCarthy Taylor yeah yeah the road
and um Country For Old No Country for
Old Men blood in yeah I haven't read any
of these books but I've seen the movie
yeah they're great yeah they're uh
they're really Bleak they don't put you
in a good mood but they're all pretty
much just about how the universe is cold
and uncaring that's the general theme
and that's what we try to get across in
this podcast yeah and uh it really
doesn't matter if you're a good person
you can't stop what's
coming you know I think we found our
reel for this
episode uh feel like we need to talk
where time just flies by with you has
this been a good one I think it's been
fun yeah there's we've got a we've got
enough was I better than was I better
than
Rodney
um how do you choose it's hard to say
about that it wasn't even better than R
we'll talk we'll talk about it after
that's a
yes uh but I think we should talk a
little bit about I mean your bio on your
website I did venture to your website
today
only person to have a clean comedy
special about being a heroin addict I
think so yeah you have that page yeah
how uh how was that experience tailoring
that to a dry bar crowd how was your old
dry bar experience in general my first
dry bar special I hate I love the people
at dry bar everybody at dry bar has been
so nice and you know I love that they
let me do those specials yeah
but you know I I made some decisions at
that first dry bar special that really
regretted
um I had enough clean material but like
2 weeks before the special I was like uh
some of this stuff is too mean and I cut
out like 12
jokes and that really affected my pacing
and I was really slow and
deliberate and stalling frankly to fill
the time and I think it's hard to watch
and
boring my second dry bar special I like
a lot more I was was originally going to
like try to raise money for this I
forget what it's called like the raise
project which is like the substance
abuse thing yeah but then that didn't
materialize and there's a chunk in it
where I talk about like uh you know I'm
glad I'm clean and everything that I had
in there for the purpose of raising
money but now it's still in there and I
think people like what was that all
but you know but I I never felt like it
was uh going to be too hard to uh to
navigate that people like religious
people they like a good Redemption story
yeah so as long as I'm careful just to
talk about how I'm clean now and I don't
use drugs anymore people are on board
with that um almost everybody is cool I
don't meet too many
like people who besched me for that like
too many actually judgmental people
right who like who's this guy talking
about drugs you know um just as long as
I was careful not to be like oh drugs
are awesome yeah you know
so yeah it it wasn't it really wasn't
that that hard just as long as all of
the jokes were about how it's in my past
and I'm now clean
and yeah I wish I had a more uh
interesting answer like well what I did
no isting yeah cuz you travel and you'll
you perform for like recovery groups
right and do that yeah it's an awesome
Niche if you want an audience that needs
a smoke break in the middle of your set
you told me they're good crowds though
you told me oh they're unbelievably good
crowds they're kind of like dry bar
crowds in a way in that it's sort of
deceptive you'll think you're better
than you are and that's great of course
but trying out new material is like
especially if you already have them it's
like I don't know if that's any good you
know and some of them are like so good
to to where you're almost annoyed by
them right it's like okay just shut up
this is that antagonistic part of your
first yeah I did this uh NA convention
in
Appalachia Appalachian drug addicts you
guys so w yeah I can't repeat what this
guy said on the dry bar uh podcast but
he comes up to me for sure say you see
that front row of people right there you
see them I go I do I want you to roast a
bleep B of them
I okay no I'm serious I'm
serious don't be mean don't be nice to
him you roast them you it's like yeah
dude I'm just going to do my
jokes and he was heckling me like the
whole whole show to to roast the people
sitting next to him like no matter what
my joke was he's like say something
about my
wife you never did you never caved no I
did the whole hour and didn't
acknowledge Him I didn't talk and I
roasted other people in the audience but
not the people he wanted me to and oh
then then you get a lot of people who
film you with their like uh Walmart
Androids every every
single recovery show I do I have to tell
a few people hey uh don't film me for
the whole time they'll sit there like
this and record me on their phones for
the whole for the whole time yeah when
people because I I do um private events
I've done shows where it's audiences
where they're not used to comedy shows I
had one where a person had the their
light on Shining at me
recording you can't have there's so many
lights on me right now we don't need
this extra that LEL of unawareness are
you still going on the road with that
gal yes at least I hope so it's not
something scheduled yet but yeah dud and
this uh Jen folweiler who I opened for
shouts out Jen folweiler
yeah I I said it weird it's full Wilder
not Fuller sheir does she have a dry bar
special no but she's kind of I feel like
she'd be great for the platform I think
she kind of self- produces her own stuff
oh okay um but yeah her audience is
since she's a new two comedy she she had
a following beforehand or people that
had never been to a comedy show before
and they they just don't know how to act
and are you really going to go watch
this who are you going to show this to
are you going to watch it later if you
just this weird Ang that's the thing
that kind of astounds me the quality is
garbage you just took up so much memory
on your phone recording an hourong video
Yeah of one you just saw you can't send
it to people it would take like hours to
send that big file yeah I don't get it
yeah yeah do you get it Taylor um if
people never been to a show
before and they think this is you know
like Taylor's Playing devil's advocate
here yeah yeah I like it you know what I
mean if You' never been to a show before
you're like oh this is my this this is a
bucketless moment maybe it's my first
time at a comedy show I want to remember
it you could can't you get that with a
couple piics do you have to take a video
of the entire thing well people take
videos of fireworks when they're going
off too which is which is equally insane
and nobody W I went to the sphere in Las
Vegas oh how was that I'll tell you
about it there are people dozens of
people all around me with their phones
out the whole time to take
a video that nobody's going to watch or
care about your cell phone does not
capture the awe inspiring show that is
the sphere just enjoy your life I'll
tell you how it was so it was an
incredible immersive experience really
impressive and amazing but I really did
not care for the message this preachy
environmental message which is fine I
care about the environment but don't
talk to me about the environment when
you use more electricity in an hour than
I use in my life
like do you know how much electricity
the sphere uses your carbon footprint is
I'm serious though that's really what
these elitists do they preach about the
environment it's like you're doing so
much worse than me it's true Leonardo
DiCaprio was he in the sphere video no
but he never shuts up about it and the
guy flies private three times a
week you're you're way worse for the
environment than me
was this a video where like the draff
comes and looks at you and stuff is yeah
there's giraffes there's all kinds of
animals and then the basically the whole
thing was like humans are terrible
scourges you should have got to the U2
show can I tell you something I talked
about this on my podcast animals aren't
Better Than
People they're not better than people
human beings are more intelligent so we
can do evil on a greater scale but
animals are terrible Twisted things a
grizzly bear will kill its own Cubs and
eat them just to get the mama bear and
heat
again they do that all the time think of
a human being did
that yeah the judge is like how come you
killed your own kid he's like well I
wanted to uh be with my wife in the
intimate way again and the judge were
like oh okay well I get it that's
fine yeah and I was reading this article
in outdoor life where a Mel Grizzly
killed all of its babies to get the mama
bear and he and then just found a a new
younger hotter mom and went and said oh
I'm going to date this one now and left
so this other Mama grizzly bear is
sitting there with no kids her whole
life just fell
apart and she probably didn't even care
that much cuz Mama Grizzlies eat their
own kids when they
started but these some people have this
sentimentalized view of nature like oh
it's you know all Harmony and beauty and
humans disrupt the whole thing yeah like
no we're part of it we're part of the
whole thing that's this is why I like
kic McCarthy McCarthy my favorite my
favorite Arthur Ki
McCarthy you're a bad influence on me
you're affecting my ability to say all
of us have messed up words today no
that's why I've always liked uh his
writing so much it just sort of
resonates with me uh like no there isn't
this harmonious thing happening that
humans are uh disrupting the whole world
is just about
survival and we just have to be smarter
than everything including Dolphins
people think dolphins dolphins are
sketchy in their own right I they are
ethically yeah yeah so you'll you'll go
into the woods and you'll see like weeds
wrapping themselves around trees sucking
the life out of these big beautiful
redwoods so it can leave live even
though it's just a pathetic
Vine so spheres Leonard
DiCaprio a
break got us a break but the show was
good
yeah well I didn't like the message but
the visuals were cool I will say I have
watched a bunch of people's not that I'd
want to watch an entire show recorded
but just kind of a quick glance inside
the Dome when they just record I have
looked at those just to be like well
that's kind of cool I want to do that so
I will say I have watched some of those
I don't think they should be recording
the whole time I think maybe the only
fair enough reason to like record
fireworks or a comedy show is in the
hope something will go wrong uh that's a
good point yeah Sig freed and Roy kind
of thing Tiger's going to snap so we
should be thankful for these people that
are yeah hopefully catching terrible
terrible moments just to be clear I like
animals we did want to clear this up
before we close and I don't feel bad for
people who get attacked by
animals when the like I was watching
this show about a guy who was cleaning
the zoo at night and he reached his arm
into to pet the Tiger and did the tiger
true or false the tiger purred and said
oh thank you for petting me I'm going to
go with false false the tiger grabbed
his arm and hung on to it and was eating
it and the guy had to call 911 and the
cops had to come and kill this tiger for
being a tiger they should have shot the
guy tiger didn't do anything wrong no is
that tiger just a bad apple no you want
to that kid had parents who are the kind
of people I'm talking about that say you
know Tigers they're just these loving
creatures that you know and if you have
good intentions they're going to sense
the good intentions oh come
on all right can you roast this tiger
for us Andy yeah show
a that tiger is a baby first of all but
also that tiger yeah it looks cute but I
wouldn't pet it and I know not to pet it
that thing could kill kill me and it
would kill me and you know what it
wouldn't think twice about it it
wouldn't spend the rest of it stayed
like oh what have I
done I killed that
guy there's that show uh Grizzly Man
with Timothy Treadwell where he goes and
lives amongst the Grizzlies in Alaska
and he finally gets eaten of course that
is that How It Ends yes this is a true
story it was a documentary and he for 13
Summers went to Alaska and everybody's
like this guy's amazing he lives with
the bears but what happened was the
first summer he kept his distance
and then every summer afterwards he got
a little bit closer and a little bit
closer and these Bears kind of grew up
with them and became familiar with him
and just thought he was like this weirdo
that lived there and he'd be like I love
you you're beautiful MW mwah mwah blow
him kisses yeah but yeah but he couldn't
Rec he couldn't reconcile when the bears
ate their cubs and stuff he like cried
he's
like cuz he couldn't calibrate it well
eventually he went back later in the
summer so all of the bear that knew him
were gone they had went to hibernate and
the bears that were in trouble they were
skinny and they were trying to survive
they had come down from the mountains to
try to get more food in them before they
go hibernate and they didn't know this
guy and he was overconfident and got
close and he got gobbled up and one of
his friends was like I think it was a
mean nasty bear who Timothy wanted to be
who Timothy wanted to be friends with I
go no it was just a hungry bear and then
the Alaska uh Wild life Patrol or
whatever went and found the bear and and
killed it and I was like come on the
bear out of what Revenge essentially
yeah like you shouldn't do
that make an example teach the other
Bears a lesson wow no you teach the
humans a lesson I've been going to
Yellowstone every year since I was a kid
and I seen so many people get gored one
time one time this guy got gored and my
dad yelled at him go s you've seen more
than one person get gored so three
people get
gored are we saying that right get gored
yeah and my dad yelled at a guy
once bison gordom right into a ditch I
think these events influenced your world
Vi about animals and he had to get T
hauled away in a hospital he got jacked
up my dad shouldn't have yelled at the
guy he like that's why you don't get
close to the
Pyon now but these stories do make it
seem like humans are worse than animals
because we are more intelligent yeah and
we
also act over overly familiar to the
point you know have you ever seen a dog
mess around with a wild
animal I think there's overlap and
stupid Behavior you know dogs will go
and bark at cougars and stuff yeah that
kangaroo you've ever you've seen that
video of the kangaroo who the guy
punches the kangar I love it that the
best thing I'll tell One More Story I've
been here for an hour when I was working
at a rehab at Cliffside Malibu the Santa
Mona mountains have an incredible coyote
problem they're just a
Scourge and they're starving mangy
coyotes and it ate one of the client's
dogs little
shitzu yeah
yeah no or not not not that where where
you going that's nature um I'm not
really going
anywhere you know a lot of your stories
Andy are people getting eaten things
getting eaten I know
yeah which I love has this been on brand
enough is this going to make
it he makes the final cut over here so
okay yeah I I've had an absolute blast
but we I think we should wrap it up here
this might be our longest one to date
yeah in a while okay Andy do you have
anything you would like to plug or say
to the audience feel free to
Nah if people like me they'll find me if
they didn't like me saying my Instagram
handle won't do diddly squat it's Andy
gold with a go at the beginning GLD go
just like the precious metal Jack yeah
okay thanks for having me this was fun
hey had a great time man thanks for
being here yeah and uh thanks to you
guys uh we we appreciate you tuning in
every week and check out Drybar
comedy.com for upcoming specials Jordans
will be dropping here soon yeah soon
keep your eye out so all right guys
we'll catch you later thank you bye
everybody
[Music]
yeah